{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522943954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522943954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522948813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522948813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522952464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522952464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522956349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522956349"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522959854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522959853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522965081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522965081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522969006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522969006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522974868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522974868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522978443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522978443"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522982481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522982481"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522986794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522986794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522989809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522989808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 87cdcad0-bc41-4e41-9f38-f5e4907117c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522999249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522999249"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522999422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522999422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548522999760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548522999760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523000904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523000904"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523001634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523001633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523004939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523004939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523005586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523005585"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523006384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523006384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523007230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523007229"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523008164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523008164"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523008852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523008852"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523011819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523011818"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523012531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523012530"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523013561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523013561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523013748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523013748"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523014514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523014514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523017579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523017579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523018402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523018401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523018470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523018470"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523019066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523019065"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523019651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523019650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523020440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523020440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523023953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523023953"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523024591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523024590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523025260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523025260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523028263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523028260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523029151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523029151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523030245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523030245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523031419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523031419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523034815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523034815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523035209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523035208"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523035836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523035836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523037049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523037048"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523037706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523037706"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523039156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523039156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523040010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523040009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523043021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523043021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523044001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523044000"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523044881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523044881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523045550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523045550"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523046589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523046588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523047873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523047872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523047891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523047891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523048767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523048767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523049864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523049864"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523052214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523052214"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523052970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523052970"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523053833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523053833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523055939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523055938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523056491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523056490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523057269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523057268"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523057784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523057784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523058587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523058586"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523059263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523059263"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523060117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523060117"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523063030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523063029"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523063833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523063832"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523065406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523065405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523065637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523065637"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523066182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523066181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523066991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523066990"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523067606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523067606"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523068664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523068663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523069158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523069158"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523071579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523071579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523072001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523072001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523072551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523072551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523073914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523073914"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523077372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523077371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523078310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523078309"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523079033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523079033"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523079256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523079256"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523079839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523079839"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523080683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523080683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523080857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523080857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523081471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523081471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523083295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523083294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523084070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523084070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523087170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523087170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523087996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523087995"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523088650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523088650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523089255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523089255"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523089648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523089647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523089851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523089851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523090583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523090583"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523093441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523093440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523094106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523094106"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523094949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523094949"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523095645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523095644"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523096428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523096428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523099017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523099016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523100199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523100199"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523100973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523100973"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523101737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523101737"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523104683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523104682"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107043"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107057"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107073"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107088"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523107984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523107984"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523108861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523108860"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523111655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523111655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523112147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523112147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523112902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523112901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523113980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523113979"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523114394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523114393"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523115108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523115107"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523118239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523118239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523119194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523119193"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523119938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523119937"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523120596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523120595"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523121511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523121510"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523124211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523124210"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523125025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523125025"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523125850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523125849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523128445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523128444"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523129077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523129077"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523129662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523129662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523130647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523130644"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523131553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523131553"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523132609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523132609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523133184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523133184"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523135864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523135863"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523135986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523135986"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 71d10428-23b9-429a-af33-9362d591b6b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523148694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523148693"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523148876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523148875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523149208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523149208"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523150365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523150364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523151099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523151099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji cha Kobole kilikuwa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523154335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523154334"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALASIRI"," userResponse":" ALASIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523154978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523154977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523155773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523155772"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523156623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523156622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523157561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523157560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIOKOTA"," userResponse":" AKIOKOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523158254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523158253"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alasiri moja Kobole alikuwa akiokota matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523161152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523161152"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHUHUDIA"," userResponse":" ALISHUHUDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523161860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523161859"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIO"," userResponse":" TUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523162893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523162892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISILOKUWA"," userResponse":" LISILOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523163077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523163077"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523163837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523163837"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alishuhudia tukio lisilokuwa la kawaida."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523166948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523166947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONA"," userResponse":" ALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523167770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523167770"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MISTARI"," userResponse":" MISTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523167833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523167833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523168429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523168428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523169012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523169011"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523169804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523169803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliona mistari ya rangi rangi angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523173330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523173330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGUSHA"," userResponse":" ALIANGUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523173966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523173965"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523174629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523174628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliangusha matunda chini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523177592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523177591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523178489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523178489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523179584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523179584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAAMBIA"," userResponse":" KUWAAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523180754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523180754"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikimbia nyumbani kuwaambia wanakijiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523184136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523184135"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAPATA"," userResponse":" ALIWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523184529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523184528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523185154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523185153"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523186367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523186366"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" WAMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523187024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523187023"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523188478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523188477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523189327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523189327"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwapata watu wote wamesimama nje wakiangalia angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523192329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523192329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523193305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523193304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523194180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523194179"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523194845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523194844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUKA"," userResponse":" SHUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523195885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523195884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523197165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523197165"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INANING"," userResponse":" INANING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523197184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523197184"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INIA"," userResponse":" INIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523198059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523198059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523199157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523199155"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kobole alisema Ni shuka maridadi inaning'inia kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523201533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523201532"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523202288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523202287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523203150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523203149"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523205260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523205260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523205817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523205817"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523206595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523206594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMWAGA"," userResponse":" ANAMWAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523207107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523207107"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523207904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523207904"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523208577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523208577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523209433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523209432"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu anamwaga rangi tofauti kutoka angani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523212368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523212367"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523213173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523213172"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523214747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523214746"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUBALIANA"," userResponse":" WALIKUBALIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523214981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523214980"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523215523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523215523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBOLE"," userResponse":" KOBOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523216329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523216328"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523216944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523216944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523218002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523218002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWAMINI"," userResponse":" WAKIMWAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523218498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523218498"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wengine walikubaliana na Kobole huku wengine wakimwamini Neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523220915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523220915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKUNDI"," userResponse":" VIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523221337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523221336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523221889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523221889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIWILI"," userResponse":" VIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523223257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523223257"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vikundi hivyo viwili vilibishana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIBISHANA"," userResponse":" VILIBISHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523226664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523226663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523227597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523227597"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523228333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523228333"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523228567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523228566"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523229163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523229163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523230018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523230017"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKEA"," userResponse":" ALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523230205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523230205"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523230831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523230830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523232663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523232662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMEKOSEA"," userResponse":" MMEKOSEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523233433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523233433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme kutoka kijiji cha mbali alitokea na kusema Mmekosea nyote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOTE"," userResponse":" NYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523236496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523236496"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523237318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523237317"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPIGA"," userResponse":" WALIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523237969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523237969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523238577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523238577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523238970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523238970"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523239166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523239166"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523239903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523239902"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walipiga mayowe Kwa hivyo ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523242808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523242807"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523243474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523243473"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523244314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523244314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523245011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523245008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523245795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523245794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523248408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523248407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523249595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523249594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMJAWAHI"," userResponse":" HUMJAWAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523250382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523250382"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523251164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523251163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwani humjawahi kuona upinde?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523254117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523254116"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256485"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256516"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523256581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523256581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523257446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523257446"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523258320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523258320"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" La u-p-i-n-d-e ni nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523261171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523261171"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIULIZA"," userResponse":" WALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523261654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523261654"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523262398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523262398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523263472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523263472"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" WAKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523263876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523263876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523264578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523264578"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliuliza wote huku wakimwangalia yule mgeni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523267796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523267795"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523268749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523268748"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523269493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523269492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523270151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523270151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523271064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523271064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Neno aliuliza Je ni wetu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WETU"," userResponse":" WETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523273741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523273740"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523274556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523274556"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523275384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523275383"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaweza kuuweka hapa?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523277969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523277969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523278593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523278593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523279179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523279178"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523280165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523280163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523281067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523281067"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523282123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523282122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEENDA"," userResponse":" AMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523282695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523282694"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523285378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523285375"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523285448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523285448"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d94fe931-9671-45bb-91a4-e38a4020d3ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_38"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mwanamme huyu alikuwa tayari ameenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523294643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523294642"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523296750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523296750"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523298891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523298890"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523302132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523302132"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523304373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523304373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523306627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523306627"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523309532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523309531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523311737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523311737"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523313950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523313949"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523317212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523317211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523319314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523319314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523321423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523321422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523324429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523324428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523326686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523326686"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523328952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523328951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523331997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523331997"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523334360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523334359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523336698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523336697"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523339766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523339766"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523341946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523341945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523344091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523344090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523347231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523347230"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523349405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523349405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523351564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523351564"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523354721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523354720"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523357121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523357120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523359515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523359514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523362655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523362655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523364957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523364957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523367221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523367220"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523370186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523370185"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523372424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523372423"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523374646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523374645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523377657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523377657"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523380020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523380020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523382372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523382371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523385478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523385477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523387889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523387889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523390270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523390269"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523393299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523393299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523395594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523395593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523397904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523397903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523401137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523401136"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523403404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523403403"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523405662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523405662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523409040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523409040"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523411488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523411487"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523413955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523413954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523416841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523416840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523419035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523419034"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523421256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523421255"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523424669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523424669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523426989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523426989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523429320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523429319"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523432478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523432477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523434731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523434731"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523436983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523436982"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523440042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523440042"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523442193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523442192"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523444350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523444350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523447506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523447505"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523449754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523449754"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523451950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523451950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523455145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523455145"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523457366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523457365"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523459571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523459571"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523462863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523462862"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523465210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523465209"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523467565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523467565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523470693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523470693"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523473052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523473050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523475408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523475407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523478840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523478838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523478922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523478922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" dab99cf0-ea4a-42d3-905d-8787901a51be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523492714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523492714"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523497514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523497514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523505102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523505102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523514935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523514935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523520627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523520627"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523526458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523526457"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523531833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523531833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523538589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523538589"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523548405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523548405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523554287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523554287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523560854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523560853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 30832e11-1a23-417d-9bcf-c5529c856a58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523571751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523571751"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_U-G-J"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523575437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523575437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_E-F-G"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523579087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523579087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_N-U-G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523583776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523583776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_O-E-G"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523587452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523587452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_A-F-G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523591344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523591344"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_I-G-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523595176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523595175"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_A-G-E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523611014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523611014"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_P-K-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523614829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523614828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_I-U-G"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523618336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523618335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_H-G-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523624082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523624081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21f4c571-d311-4953-9588-f6a5f3eda0d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_G_H-G-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523633774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523633773"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523634323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523634322"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523635318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523635317"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523635891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523635890"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523636618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523636618"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523639280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523639278"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523639575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523639575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523640259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523640258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523640851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523640850"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523641702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523641701"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523642537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523642537"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523642988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523642987"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523643868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523643868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523645216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523645216"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523646453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523646452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523646475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523646474"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523646925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523646924"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523647509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523647508"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523650302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523650300"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523651110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523651109"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523652201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523652201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523652836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523652835"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwoa mwanamke mrembo sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523655931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523655930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523656220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523656220"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523656911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523656911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523657160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523657160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523657603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523657603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523658279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523658278"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523658701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523658699"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523659700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523659700"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523661107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523661106"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523661621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523661620"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523662916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523662916"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523663755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523663755"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523664713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523664712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523667259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523667258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523668482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523668482"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523669387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523669387"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523669888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523669888"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523670989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523670988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUNIA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523671705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523671705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe alifurahi sana na kujivunia mkewe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523674227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523674226"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523675003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523675003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523675216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523675215"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523675811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523675811"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523676689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523676688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523677851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523677849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523678414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523678414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523679502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523679502"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWACHA"," userResponse":" ALIMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523680160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523680160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523681039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523681039"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523682036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523682036"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523682719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523682719"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523683333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523683333"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523683815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523683815"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523684592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523684592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAMA"," userResponse":" KUKAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523685131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523685130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523685150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523685150"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523687727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523687727"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523688002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523688001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523688809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523688809"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523689464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523689464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523690801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523690800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHIA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523691562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523691561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523691809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523691808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523692591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523692590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523693537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523693537"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523694265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523694265"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMA"," userResponse":" PEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523695266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523695266"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523695351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523695351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523695907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523695907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa ni kawaida yake kumwachia kibuyu cha maziwa mahali pema ndani ya nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523698848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523698848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523699363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523699363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523700173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523700173"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523701006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523701006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBAKI"," userResponse":" ALIBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523701847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523701847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523703256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523703256"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523703509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523703509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523704346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523704345"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWA"," userResponse":" KUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523705074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523705074"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523705731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523705731"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523706405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523706405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523707093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523707092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523707814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523707813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523710571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523710570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523712057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523712056"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANGEKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523712735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523712735"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMBANI"," userResponse":" CHUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523712915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523712915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523713618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523713617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake angekimbia chumbani na kumlea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLEA"," userResponse":" KUMLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523716575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523716574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523717350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523717350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523718008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523718008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBUYU"," userResponse":" KIBUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523718239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523718238"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523718903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523718903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523720210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523720210"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIPATIKANA"," userResponse":" KILIPATIKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523720888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523720887"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKIWA"," userResponse":" KIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523721514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523721513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523724434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523724434"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523725572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523725572"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILISHANGAZA"," userResponse":" ILISHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523726504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523726504"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523729558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523729558"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523730359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523730358"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523731199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523731199"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523732471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523732471"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEJUA"," userResponse":" ALIYEJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523733107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523733107"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523734168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523734167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUNYWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523734877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523734876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna hata mmoja aliyejua nani alikunywa maziwa."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523738229","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523738228"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523738772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523738771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523740119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523740119"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWARIFU"," userResponse":" ALIMWARIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523740772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523740771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523741718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523741718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUKIO"," userResponse":" MATUKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523742280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523742279"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523745091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523745090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMEWE"," userResponse":" MUMEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523745959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523745958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523747279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523747278"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELELEZA"," userResponse":" KUPELELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523748197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523748196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523748877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523748876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APATE"," userResponse":" APATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523749664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523749663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKWELI"," userResponse":" UKWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523750542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523750542"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumewe akaamua kupeleleza ili apate ukweli kamili."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMILI"," userResponse":" KAMILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523753520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523753519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523754214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523754213"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523755389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523755388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523756131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523756131"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523756215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523756215"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523756893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523756892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523757478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523757478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523758711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523758710"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASHANGAA"," userResponse":" AKASHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523759368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523759364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523760140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523760140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523760935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523760934"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKINYWA"," userResponse":" AKINYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523761181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523761180"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523762085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523762084"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMALIZA"," userResponse":" KUMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523762797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523762796"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana huyo alijificha ndani ya nyumba na akashangaa kuona mtoto akinywa na kumaliza maziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523765337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523765337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523765903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523765903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523766157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523766156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523767390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523767390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa jambo la kushangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAZA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523770309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523770307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523770582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523770581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523771314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523771314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523772560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523772560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" WALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523773254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523773254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523774783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523774783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523775640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523775640"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWACHA"," userResponse":" KUMWACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523776304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523776304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523776806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523776804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523777599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523777599"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALALE"," userResponse":" ALALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523778566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523778565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523779320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523779319"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAHAME"," userResponse":" WAHAME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523779945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523779945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523780498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523780498"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523781155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523781155"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523781390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523781389"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523782092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523782091"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mume na mkewe walipogundua haya waliamua kumwacha mtoto huyo alale kisha wahame mahali pale wakati wa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523784911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523784910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523785534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523785533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523786537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523786537"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523787371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523787371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHWA"," userResponse":" ALIACHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523787594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523787594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523788257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523788257"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523788810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523788810"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523792002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523792001"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWACHIA"," userResponse":" WALIMWACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523792813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523792813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523792826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523792826"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523794148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523794148"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGAMIA"," userResponse":" NGAMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523794591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523794591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523795375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523795375"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walimwachia ng'ombe ngamia na mbuzi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523798581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523798581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523798953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523798952"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523800406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523800405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOAMKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523802285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523802284"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUTA"," userResponse":" AKAKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523803021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523803021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523804516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523804515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOACHIWA"," userResponse":" ALIOACHIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523804759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523804758"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523805776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523805776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523805842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523805842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523806917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523806917"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523807861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523807861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKIWA"," userResponse":" YAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523808634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523808634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVU"," userResponse":" TULIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523809167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523809167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto huyu alipoamka akakuta wanyama alioachiwa na mazingira ya nyumbani yakiwa tulivu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523812860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523812860"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523813478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523813478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523814462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523814462"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMUA"," userResponse":" AKAAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523815545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523815545"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAUA"," userResponse":" KUWAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523815967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523815967"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523816851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523816851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523818118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523818117"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523818602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523818601"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523818617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523818617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikasirika na akaamua kuwaua hao wanyama isipokuwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523821414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523821413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINGIA"," userResponse":" ALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523822235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523822234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523822506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523822505"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523823069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523823068"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523823082","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523823082"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliingia tumboni mwa ng'ombe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523826201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523826201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523826212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523826212"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523827336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523827335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523828587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523828587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523829820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523829819"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523830575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523830575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523831625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523831625"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPITA"," userResponse":" AKAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523832324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523832323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523833111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523833110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWONA"," userResponse":" KUMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523833585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523833585"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523833604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523833604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523834218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523834217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523835218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523835217"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523837076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523837076"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAMCHINJA"," userResponse":" NITAMCHINJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523837602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523837602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523837623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523837623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523838100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523838099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523838784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523838783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIPATE"," userResponse":" NIPATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523839680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523839678"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alipokuwa malishoni mwanamume fulani akapita na kumwona ng'ombe yule akasema Nitamchinja ng'ombe huyu nipate kitoweo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITOWEO"," userResponse":" KITOWEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523842539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523842539"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMCHOMA"," userResponse":" AKAMCHOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523842835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523842835"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523843536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523843536"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUKI"," userResponse":" MKUKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523844275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523844275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akamchoma kwa mkuki akafa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFA"," userResponse":" AKAFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523847730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523847730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523848987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523848987"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMCHUNA"," userResponse":" AKIMCHUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523849784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523849783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523850895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523850894"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIKIA"," userResponse":" AKASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523851699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523851698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523853047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523853046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKITOKEA"," userResponse":" IKITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523853492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523853491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523853939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523853938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523854197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523854196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523854683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523854682"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523854694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523854694"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523856768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523856766"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINIUMIZE"," userResponse":" USINIUMIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523857502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523857501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523858589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523858589"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akimchuna ngozi akasikia sauti ikitokea kwenye tumbo la ng'ombe Usiniumize niko tumboni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523861699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523861699"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523861922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523861922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523862996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523862996"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523864075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523864075"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKA"," userResponse":" AKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523864666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523864666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523864942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523864942"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523865533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523865533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523865552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523865551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523866317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523866316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523866855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523866854"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523868003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523868003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJINATA"," userResponse":" KUJINATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523868643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523868642"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523869098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523869098"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523869335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523869335"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523870294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523870294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523870654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523870653"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523873364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523873363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMUME"," userResponse":" MWANAMUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523874304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523874303"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOGOPA"," userResponse":" ALIOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523875020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523875020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523875968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523875967"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523876572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523876572"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523877326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523877325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523877804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523877803"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523878268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523878266"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamume aliogopa na kukimbia bila kula ile nyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523881656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523881655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523882431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523882430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523883622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523883622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHINJIA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHINJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523884131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523884131"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523884718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523884717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523885357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523885357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523885548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523885547"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUME"," userResponse":" DUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523887225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523887224"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipofika nyumbani alimchinjia huyo mtoto kondoo dume aliyenona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYENONA"," userResponse":" ALIYENONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523890301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523890301"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523890522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523890522"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523891482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523891481"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMIUJIZA"," userResponse":" KIMIUJIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523892416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523892415"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALA"," userResponse":" AKALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523894221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523894221"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFURAHI"," userResponse":" AKAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523894915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523894914"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523895538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523895538"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523895737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523895736"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523896702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523896702"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" AKAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523897326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523897326"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523899858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523899854"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523899940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523899939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" efa65ced-e2de-40cf-ade0-c5491975bb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523911623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523911622"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523912004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523912003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523912498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523912498"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523912849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523912849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523913270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523913269"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523913753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523913752"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523913989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523913989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523917212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523917211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523917256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523917256"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523917983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523917982"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523918382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523918382"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523918686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523918685"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523918901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523918900"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523919103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523919102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523919428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523919427"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523919660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523919659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523922849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523922849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523923260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523923259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523925881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523925881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523926091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523926090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523926301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523926301"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523929830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523929830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523933620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523933619"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523934653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523934650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523937388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523937387"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523937772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523937771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523938262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523938262"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523938611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523938611"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523939027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523939026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523939508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523939508"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523939744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523939743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523942995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523942995"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523943040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523943038"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523943762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523943761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523944162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523944161"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523944464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523944463"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523944677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523944677"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523944881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523944881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523945201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523945201"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523945434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523945433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523948094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523948093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523948160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523948160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523987908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523987907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 21501db5-2f0e-4e7d-9eec-32b8658db992"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524030453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524030453"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524037112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524037112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_W_G"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524043751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524043751"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524050407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524050407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_G_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524057032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524057032"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_D_G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524063708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524063708"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_G_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524071189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524071189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_G_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524081390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524081390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_G_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524087600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524087599"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_G_Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524095121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524095121"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_G_Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524101783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524101783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_W_G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524109294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524109293"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_W_G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524119495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524119495"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_W_G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524126139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524126139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_G_CH"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524132784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524132783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:G..G.all.10.rand.say.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524141803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524141802"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524357463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524357461"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6e8ef77b-c3f0-4875-9ff9-f077aafe701a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_G..G.all.10.rand.say.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_G_B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524357585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524357585"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" f7a9422f-5d05-4da9-a8a4-1f1f0c282656"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524368822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524368821"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524370878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524370878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524372487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524372486"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524377971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524377971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524379575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524379574"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524387491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524387490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524389093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524389093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524391743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524391742"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524393351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524393350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524396512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524396512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524398102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524398102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524401202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524401202"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524402807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524402806"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524407814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524407813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524409385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524409384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524412344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524412344"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524413908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524413908"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524432104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524432104"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524435028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524435027"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524439827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524439827"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524441413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524441412"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524444052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524444051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524445654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524445654"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524448938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524448938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524450529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524450528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524453074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524453074"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524454638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524454638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524461652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524461652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524463224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524463224"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524468535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524468535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524470129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524470129"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524473836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524473836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524475430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524475430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524483501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524483500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524485101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524485101"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524488369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524488369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524489999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524489998"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524492288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524492287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524493892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524493892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524500271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524500271"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524501888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524501887"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524563801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524563800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524565418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524565418"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524571904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524571903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524573930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524573929"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524574092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524574092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 69737e50-2b7a-4f20-904c-86e4bfc5d937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524585484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524585484"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524591727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524591727"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524596962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524596962"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524602489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524602489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524608032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524608032"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524613456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524613456"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524618468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524618468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524624019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524624019"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524628835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524628835"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524633967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524633967"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524640536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524640535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" d937e0de-36ca-4a1a-afe3-c56125211126"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524652339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524652338"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524655930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524655930"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524659813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524659812"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524663302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524663302"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524666784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524666784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524670323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524670323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524674138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524674138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524677926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524677926"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524681612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524681612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524685264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524685264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524689021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524689020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524692902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524692902"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524696520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524696520"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524702983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524702983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524707039","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524707039"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524711076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524711076"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524715852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524715852"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524719545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524719545"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524723429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524723429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524727140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524727140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524730733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524730733"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524734351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524734350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524738259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524738259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524742358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524742357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524748114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524748113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525021901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525021899"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 5b717f02-3b00-44e1-b4ae-aeab3283732a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525022004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525022003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 093828b1-0fda-4464-9886-bfc6a5222939"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525034350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525034350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525036513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525036513"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525038659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525038659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525041891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525041891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525044138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525044138"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525046403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525046403"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525049267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525049267"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525051491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525051490"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525053711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525053710"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525057006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525057006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525059122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525059122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525061169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525061169"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525064102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525064102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525066302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525066302"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525068490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525068489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525071535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525071535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525073893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525073893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525076276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525076274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525079353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525079352"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525081494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525081494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525083621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525083621"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525086800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525086799"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525088998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525088998"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525091197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525091196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525094391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525094390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525096805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525096805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525099209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525099208"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525102393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525102392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525104646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525104645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525106904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525106904"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525109938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525109937"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525112172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525112170"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525114414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525114413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525117387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525117386"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525119759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525119758"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525122091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525122090"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525125250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525125249"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525127617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525127617"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525130018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525130016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525133008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525133007"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525135306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525135306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525137607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525137606"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525140851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525140851"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525143131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525143130"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525145336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525145336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525148669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525148668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525151046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525151046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525153440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525153440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525156241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525156241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525158425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525158424"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525160653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525160651"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525164053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525164053"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525166412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525166411"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525168711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525168711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525171831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525171830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525174134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525174133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525176404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525176404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525179368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525179367"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525181456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525181456"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525183588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525183587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525186709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525186708"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525188948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525188948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525191233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525191232"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525194486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525194486"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525196703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525196703"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525198946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525198944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525202224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525202222"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525204568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525204568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525206946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525206945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525210076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525210076"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525212406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525212405"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525214790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525214790"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525218198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525218195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525218312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525218312"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4b631749-a041-47d7-a6f9-878bfe1e3d77"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525252133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525252132"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525254236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525254236"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525256300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525256300"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525259419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525259419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525261636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525261636"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525263823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525263823"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525266593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525266593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525268733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525268733"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525270872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525270872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525274063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525274063"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525276121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525276121"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525278152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525278152"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525281093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525281093"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525283304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525283304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525285527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525285527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525288497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525288497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525290809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525290809"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525293098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525293098"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525296075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525296075"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525298162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525298162"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525300251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525300251"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525303314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525303314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525305449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525305449"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525307605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525307604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525310828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525310827"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525313250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525313250"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525315685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525315683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525318816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525318816"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525321103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525321103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525323313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525323312"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525326258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525326258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525328448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525328447"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525330677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525330677"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525333634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525333633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525335971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525335971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525338321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525338321"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525341357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525341357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525343688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525343688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525346081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525346081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525349033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525349033"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525351309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525351309"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525353544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525353543"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525356695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525356695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525358922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525358921"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525361160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525361160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525364404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525364404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525366802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525366802"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525369248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525369247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525372112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525372112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525374306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525374306"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525376437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525376437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525379829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525379829"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525382142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525382142"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525384415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525384415"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525387510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525387509"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525389779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525389779"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525392007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525392007"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525394984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525394984"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525397087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525397087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525399186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525399186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525402219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525402219"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525404417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525404416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525406636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525406636"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525409775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525409774"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525411982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525411981"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525414240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525414240"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525417452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525417451"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525419749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525419749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525422037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525422037"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525425167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525425167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525427521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525427520"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525429877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525429877"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525433268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525433266"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525433367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525433367"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525476483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525476483"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8e97a34a-f2b1-411e-a62b-2a2725a67d2d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525502196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525502196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_S-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525508240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525508240"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-CH-K"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525511841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525511840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_I-H-F"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525515525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525515525"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-M-H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525519178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525519177"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-N"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525522521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525522521"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-S-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525525984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525525984"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-N"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525529634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525529634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-H-W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525533253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525533253"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-W-E"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525536682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525536682"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525542413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525542412"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 411abe39-2795-47a4-85fa-845d0836aee0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-E-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525554943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525554942"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525555166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525555166"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525556129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525556129"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525557409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525557408"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525560386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525560385"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525561237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525561237"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525561562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525561562"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525562810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525562810"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525566397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525566396"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525567381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525567381"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525567634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525567634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525568602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525568602"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525571531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525571531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525572581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525572580"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525573062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525573062"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525577645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525577645"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525577709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525577708"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 4c98336f-f752-4ecb-9262-ea875e26ffed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525588239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525588239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525588468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525588468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525589457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525589456"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525590743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525590743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525593697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525593697"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525594565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525594565"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525594879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525594879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525596136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525596136"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525599703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525599702"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525600698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525600695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525600958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525600958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525601913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525601912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525604834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525604834"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525605883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525605882"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525606366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525606366"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525610896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525610895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525610994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525610994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" c1828791-1eb7-44bd-a07f-eff7e8770387"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525631293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525631293"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_D_W"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525637941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525637941"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_L_U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525644576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525644576"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_L_H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525651218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525651218"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_H_A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525657858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525657857"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525664555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525664555"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_I_J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525671261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525671261"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_N_H"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525677926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525677926"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_U_O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525684582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525684582"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_H_U"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525691257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525691257"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_H_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525704404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525704403"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_U_H_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525768493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525768492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 8932b4f8-b1bb-48c2-9527-d0c0ea3dd331"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.22"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_U_H_D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525791906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525791906"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6c13e791-1f36-4cd0-8a16-c3c6c50af5c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525797075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525797075"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6c13e791-1f36-4cd0-8a16-c3c6c50af5c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525803163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525803163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6c13e791-1f36-4cd0-8a16-c3c6c50af5c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548525805603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548525805603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190126_201500"," gameId":" 6c13e791-1f36-4cd0-8a16-c3c6c50af5c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}